export default data = [
  {
      question: "Nowadays many companies adopt a ______ work schedule which allows their employees to decide when to arrive at work—from as early as 6 a.m. to as late as 11 a.m.",
      options: ["relative","severe","primitive","flexible"],
      correct_option: "flexible"
  },
  {
      question: "To teach children right from wrong, some parents will ______ their children when they behave well and punish them when they misbehave.",
      options: ["settle","declare","reward","neglect"],
      correct_option: "reward"
  },
  {
      question: "To stick to a tight budget, Robert bought a more ______ LED TV instead of a fancy, expensive 3D TV.",
      options: ["technical","significant","affordable","expressive"],
      correct_option: "affordable"
  },
  {
      question: "David’s new book made it to the best-seller list because of its beautiful ______ and amusing stories.",
      options: ["operations","illustrations","engagements","accomplishments"],
      correct_option: "illustrations"
  },
  {
      question: "The airport was closed because of the snowstorm, and our ______ for Paris had to be delayed until the following day. ",
      options: ["movement","registration","tendency","departure"],
      correct_option: "departure"
  },
  {
      question: "The moment the students felt the earthquake, they ran ______ out of the classroom to an open area outside. ",
      options: ["swiftly","nearly","loosely","formally"],
      correct_option: "swiftly"
  },
  {
      question: "The ______ capacity of this elevator is 400 kilograms. For safety reasons, it shouldn’t be overloaded. ",
      options: ["delicate","automatic","essential","maximum"],
      correct_option: "maximum"
  },
  {
      question: "An open display of ______ behavior between men and women, such as hugging and kissing, is not allowed in some conservative societies.",
      options: ["intimate","ashamed","earnest","urgent"],
      correct_option: "intimate"
  },
  {
      question: "When taking medicine, we should read the instructions on the ______ carefully because they provide important information such as how and when to take it. ",
      options: ["medals","quotes","labels","recipes"],
      correct_option: "labels"
  },
  {
      question: "The angry passengers argued ______ with the airline staff because their flight was cancelled without any reason. ",
      options: ["evidently","furiously","obediently","suspiciously"],
      correct_option: "furiously"
  },
  {
      question: "To ______ the new product, the company offered some free samples before they officially launched it.",
      options: ["contribute","impress","promote","estimate"],
      correct_option: "promote"
  },
  {
      question: "I was worried about my first overseas trip, but my father ______ me that he would help plan the trip so that nothing would go wrong. ",
      options: ["rescued","assured","inspired","conveyed"],
      correct_option: "assured"
  },
  {
      question: "The recent cooking oil scandals have led to calls for tougher ______ of sales of food products.  ",
      options: ["tolerance","guarantee","regulation","distribution"],
      correct_option: "regulation"
  },
  {
      question: "John should ______ more often with his friends and family after work, instead of staying in his room to play computer games. ",
      options: ["explore","interact","negotiate","participate"],
      correct_option: "interact"
  },
  {
      question: "To prevent the spread of the Ebola virus from West Africa to the rest of the world, many airports have begun Ebola ______ for passengers from the infected areas.",
      options: ["screenings","listings","clippings","blockings"],
      correct_option: "screenings"
  },
]
